Adrian Zinko



hello@adrianzinko.com



linkedin.com/in/adrian-zinko



(+48) 505899082



https://adrianzinko.com

Summary

As a software developer with 3 years of experience in the industry, I have a strong understanding of the JavaScript language working on commercial projects using React and Angular.

I have a basic understanding of backend development with NodeJS (Express, NestJS) and experience working with AWS, Docker, and CI/CD.

I've also worked in Scrum environments and have experience as a technical recruiter. In addition I hosted a couple of internal JS campanies.

I am a well-rounded professional with a mix of technical and recruitment experience, always looking to improve and enhance my skillset. A team player who is dedicated to delivering quality results. Throughout my dev growth, I'm successively adopting pragmatic & reliable solutions to encountered challenges.

Main tech stack:

React | Angular | Node | Typescript | RxJS NextJS | Gatsby | GraphQL | Docker

Besides, I like cats and mountains.

https://github.com/adrianghub

Experience



JavaScript Developer

Boldare

Apr 2022 - Present (11 months)

So far, I was responsible mainly for the Frontend Development of apps for various clients.

In September 2022 I finished Node Backend Development workshops and for my next steps, I'm planning to move toward Backend Development.

Currently, I'm working on an internal application (frontend built from scratch on Angular 14+) for a client in the US.



Junior JavaScript Developer

Boldare

Jan 2022 - Apr 2022 (4 months)

Throughout the first 4 months in the company, I've worked on various smaller products.

I've implemented an extensive search on the company's blog. I've extended functionality for the company's automation Slack bot tool (scheduled chart with data).

I had the opportunity to provide early development estimation for a couple of products.

I've also gathered my first experience working in decentralized management, Holacracy, upon which the company is based. At the end of the trial period, I was promoted.

B Frontend Developer

Billennium

Nov 2021 - Jan 2022 (3 months)

I joined a German startup for a 6 weeks sprint to support the team working on the UNICEF website.

Junior JavaScript Developer

ArdentCode

Jun 2021 - Nov 2021 (6 months)

I was responsible for improving test coverage for React components/utils/services. With a group of 4 teammates, I've created an MVP app (PWA) suited entirely for mobile devices. The app was designed for Botanics. The solution was the real-time navigation for the special maps provided by them. Maps could be uploaded through the app and stored locally on each device's browser (with the help of IndexedDB).

Besides, I've integrated measurements from Garmin devices with the company's internal app. Integration consists of Garmin OAuth and .fitfile conversion. There were also bugs to fix as well as new features to implement.

Junior Webmaster

Artefakt Sp. z o.o. sp. k.

Nov 2020 - Sep 2021 (11 months)

I was responsible for page optimization regarding the Google Search Engine. I relied mainly on guidance from SEO specialists. The team consisted of around 15 people, mostly Webmasters, a Team leader, and 1 fullstack programmer.

Software Engineer Intern

Allegro

Jun 2020 - Sep 2020 (4 months)

For the first time, I had an experience working in an Agile environment. My responsibilities were spread between unit tests, new components implementation, and code refactoring. I was working in a team of around 10 people. Together we were developing the e-commerce product offer page.

Junior SEO Assistant

Pikseo Sp. z o. o. Sp. k.

Jan 2020 - Jun 2020 (6 months)

I've joined the company as an SEO Specialist Assistant. Throughout my work there I've optimized clients' websites (WordPress and other CMS) for Google Search Engines.

Student

DBMaster

Feb 2020 - May 2020 (4 months)

DBMaster Course - 12-week program - Oracle, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Microsoft SQL Server

Junior PHP Developer

Rubycon Sp.z o.o.

Sep 2019 - Nov 2019 (3 months)

I joined as a Junior programmer to work mainly on SQL databases, building queries, and managing tables based on task requirements. I've also written unit & integration tests for PHP modules.



WTF: Co ten frontend

May 2019 - Aug 2019 (4 months)

A 12-week frontend learning program run by a trainer with several years of experience in broadly understood web development - Maciej Korsan

Miles Kitchen Helper

AmRest

Oct 2017 - Jun 2018 (9 months)



Kitchen Food Server

Vibrant Futures May 2017 - Sep 2017 (5 months)

Education



Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Information Technology 2017 - 2021



Bachelor's degree, Information Technology 2019 - Present Erasmus exchange studies 01.19 - 06.19

Licenses & Certifications

Cambridge English Assessment B2/C1 - Cambridge College

jn JavaScript Code Challenges - LinkedIn

Node.js for JavaScript Developers - NobleProg Polska 686127

Clifton Strengths - Tracy Ho, Executive Coach & Corporate Trainer | Gallup CliftonStrengths & DiSC Certified

Skills

Figma (Software) • Angular • RxJS • Storybook • Jest • Google Material Design • TypeScript • IndexedDB • SCSS • Agile Project Management